centene.com 2005-11-23

# Centene Corporation - Privacy Policy

Centene Corporation is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our information gathering and dissemination practices. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact Centene at the e-mail address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

* **WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED.**  
We collect a limited amount of personal information from you in certain areas of the Centene web site (the "Site") for various reasons. The following is a description of what information is collected:

Registration Information.  
Registration is necessary to use certain areas of the Site. When you register at the Site, we ask you for a few items of personal information. You are also given the option to provide other information such as your interests, education, income and occupation. All of this optional information is used to deliver a more personal and pertinent experience for users of the Site.

Other third party features of the Site may require a separate registration. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third party features before providing personally identifiable information. Centene is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

IP Addresses.  
An IP address is a number assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. As part of the protocol of the Internet, web servers can identify your computer by its IP address. In addition, web servers may be able to identify the type of browser and/or type of computer you are using. MHS collects IP addresses and related information for the purposes of system administration, to assess the traffic to the Site, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to maintain and improve the Site. We do not link IP addresses to your personally identifiable information. We can and will use IP addresses, however, to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Web Site Terms and Conditions or to protect our service, the Site, customers or others.

Use Of Cookies.  
Cookies are small bits of information that some web sites (including the Site) transfer to an individual's hard drive for research purposes. Centene uses cookies to analyze the traffic, such as total visitors and pages viewed on the Site, and make improvements based on the data we collect. Centene never saves passwords or credit card information in cookies.

The use of cookies has become a standard in the industry, especially at web sites that provide any kind of personalized service. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can usually set your browser to refuse cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you refuse cookies, you may not be able to use some of the functionality of the Site. The Site's advertisers and other partners may also use cookies in connection with the services and web sites to which the Site links. We do not control these cookies.

* **WHO IS COLLECTING THIS INFORMATION.**  
Centene collects the information described above via the Site. In the case of third party features such as advertising, co-branded areas or links to other web sites, such third parties may also collect information. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third parties before providing personally identifiable information. Centene is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

* **HOW COLLECTED INFORMATION IS USED.**

In General.  
Centene uses registration information to learn more about how visitors use the Site and to measure areas of interest. This allows Centene to build features and functionality that will enhance your Site experience. We also may use the registration information to filter out those who but do not comply with the Web Site Terms and Conditions. If you so choose when you register, registration information might also be used to send you information about new features and services on the Site or offered by Centene, or to send you information from selected third party product or service providers. We might also use this information to respond to e-mails, provide customer support, enforce our Web Site Terms and Conditions or other similar matters. Aggregate information is also used to help us run and maintain the Site, study traffic patterns and generally learn about the usage of the Site. Some of this aggregate information may be used to help us set advertising rates, determine advertising fees, and attract advertisers and co-branding partners.

Unrelated Companies.  
Centene occasionally shares limited customer information with companies we hire to provide operational, marketing, or advertising support, companies that help us distribute our products and services, or companies that provide products and services we want to offer. The companies we choose must satisfy our security and privacy requirements. We share your information with these companies only if they agree to treat it confidentially and only if it is legally permissible to do so. We limit the information we provide these companies to what we reasonably believe they "need to know" in connection with their agreement with Centene and we don't permit them to use our customer information for any purposes outside our oversight or control.

Sometimes a law, court order, or other judicial or administrative process requires us to provide information to a government authority or party to a private lawsuit. We will provide the information that we in good faith believe is required to comply with the law, order, or other process. We may also have to disclose certain information in court documents if we have to bring an action against you, for example, to collect a debt you owe us.

* **CHOICES IN THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISTRIBUTION OF INFORMATION.**  
At the time of registration, you are given a choice whether you want to receive information about new features, events, offers and special coverage on the Site and about special offers from Centene's partners. When you register, you must click in a box if you do not want to receive either type of information. Unless you affirmatively choose not to receive these materials, your registration information may be used to send you this information.

It is important to know that you may inadvertently provide personally identifiable information to third parties through your postings to a forum or participation in a chat session and we have no way to limit their use of the information you may provide. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online (for example, in forums, message boards or chat sessions) that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While we strive to protect our user's personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you voluntarily disclose online and you do so at your own risk.

* **WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED.**  
Except for your choices described above, we will not knowingly disclose or authorize the disclosure of personal identifiable information (other than aggregate statistical information) to any third party without your consent unless (1) we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Web Site Terms and Conditions or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Centene's rights or property, other Site users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities or (2) we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

* **CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13 YEARS.**  
In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Centene will not knowingly collect or accept personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13 without a parent's or guardians prior consent. Centene will also allow the parent or guardian of a registered user under the age of 13 to review, update, change, delete or refuse to permit further collection of any and all information collected by the Site. A child's personally identifiable information will be treated with the same care and respect as an adult's information. To change, update, review, delete or refuse to permit further collection of your child's information, please send an e-mail to: [communication@centene.com](mailto:communication@centene.com), or a letter via postal mail to:

Centene Corporation  
Centene Place  
7711 Carondelet Ave., Suite 500  
St. Louis, MO 63105  
Attn: Children's Privacy Information

* **LINKS TO OTHER SITES.**  
While you are using the Site, you may be linked or directed to other third party web sites outside the Site that are beyond Centene's control. Each of these third parties may have a privacy policy different from that of Centene. These links and banners may take you to the web sites of advertisers, sponsors and co-branding partners. Centene is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. These other web sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third party web sites before providing personally identifiable information.

* **HOW YOU MAY CHANGE, CORRECT YOUR REGISTRATION INFORMATION.**  
If you want to change, correct, update or delete your registration information, please contact Centene via e-mail at: [communication@centene.com](mailto:communication@centene.com), or send your request to:

Centene Corporation  
Centene Place  
7711 Carondelet Ave., Suite 500  
St. Louis, MO 63105  
Attn: Registration Information Correction

and the necessary revisions will be made. This provision applies only to registration information collected via the Site.

* **SECURITY PROCEDURES WE USE.**  
We are very concerned with the security of your personally identifiable information and take great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.

Once we receive your information, we take appropriate steps that we believe are reasonable to protect the security of your data on our system, both internally and from outsiders, and to ensure the integrity of the data we collect. We use a combination of technological and policy methods to protect this data. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Please be aware that Centene will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail.

* **CHANGES IN THESE TERMS.**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and will post notices on the Site at the time of any material changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

If you have questions or concerns regarding Centene Corporation's Privacy Policy, please e-mail [communication@centene.com](mailto:communication@centene.com).
